恭喜你走到了这一步。
Congratulations on making it this far.
你已经学习了如何使用 Claude Code
You've learned how to use Claude Code
来探索、测试、重构和调试代码库。
to explore, test, refactor, and debug code bases.
为了充分发挥 Claude Code 的威力，
You can make the best out of Claude Code
请给它清晰的指令，
when you give it clear instructions,
明确当前的上下文信息，
clarify the context,
并指向代码库中相关的特定文件。
and point it to the relevant files in your codebase.
请务必将你的代码库规范添加到 CLAUDE.md 文件中，
Make sure to add your codebase rules to CLAUDE.md
以及任何你希望
and any information that you'd like
Claude Code 记住的项目信息。
Claude Code to remember about your project.
你可以考虑扩展 Claude Code 的能力，
Consider extending Claude Code capabilities
将其连接到如 Playwright 和 Figma 等 MCP 服务器。
and connecting it to MCP servers like Playwright and Figma.
感谢你与我一起开启这段旅程。
Thank you for joining me on this journey.
我迫不及待地想看到你使用 Claude Code 构建出的作品。
and I can't wait to see what you'll build with Claude Code.